Guide to the John Noble papers, 1957-2016.
Noble, John papers,
- Political, 1975-1993
  - New York State Assembly, May 9, 1983, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Rules of the Greece Democratic Committee, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - State of New York in Assembly, No. 8529, January 13, 1986, 1986-01-13 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ephemera (magnets, pins, flag, Colt 1987 calendar), Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 33)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Sexuality Publications Collected by John Noble - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.
Blade California, 2011-05, Vol. 20 Iss. 2
CRUISE/AROUND THE CLOCK, 1985-08-23, Vol. 2 No. 28
The Empty Closet, 1992-10, No. 241; 1992-12-1993-01, No. 243; 2001-07, No. 337; 2008-10, No. 417; 2011-06, No. 446; 2012-08, No. 459; 2016-05, No. 500; 2016-07, No. 502; 2016-09-2017-01, No. 504-507
Florida Agenda, 2012-02-09, Iss. 116; 2015-12-10, Iss. 316
Ghighway, 2000
GUY, 2015-11-26, #314; 2015-12-10, #316
ImageOut - the Rochester Lesbian & Gay Film & Video Festival, 2004-10-08-2004-10-17
Lambda Rising News, Winter 1990
The Leather Journal, 2012-02, Iss. 263; 2015-11-2015-12, Iss. 290
mark, 2012-02-09-2012-02-16, #116-117
South Florida Gay News.com, 2012-02-08-2012-02-15, Vol. 3 Iss. 6-7; 2015-12-02-2015-12-09, Vol. 6 Iss. 48-49
The Washington Blade, 1998-11-06, Vol. 29 No. 45; 2010-12-10, Vol. 41 Iss. 50
SEPARATED MATERIAL NOT RETAINED
5th Freedom, 1980-12
The Advocate, various issues from 1982-1987, 1997-04, 2012-05, 2018-02-2018-03
After Dark, 1978-03, 1979-08
The Blade/The Washington Blade, 1977-10, No. 10; 1985-05-03, Vol. 16 No. 18
The Body Positive, 1989-06, Vol. 2 No. 5
Chorus Lines, 1985-09, Vol. 2
Christopher Street, 1984-1985, Iss. 89, 93
Connection, 1984-02-08-1984-02-22, Vol. 3 No. 6
DNA, 2011, No. 138
The Empty Closet, 1977-04, Iss. 71; 1977-11, Iss. 77; 1978-09, Iss. 86; 1981-03, Iss. 114; 1986-06, Iss. 171; 1987-04, Iss. 180; 1998-11, Iss. 308
Gay Community News - The Gay Weekly, 1976-04-10, Vol. 3 No. 41; 1976-04-24, Vol. 3 No. 43; 1976-06-26, Vol. 3 No. 52; 1976-07-17-1976-07-24, Vol. 4 No. 3-4; 1976-08-14-1976-08-21, Vol. 4 No. 7-8; 1976-09-04-1976-09-18, Vol. 4 No. 10-12; 1977-02-26, Vol. 4 No. 35; 1977-03-12-1977-04-02, Vol. 4 No. 37-40; 1977-05-21, Vol. 4 No. 47; 1977-07-09, Vol. 5 No. 2; 1977-07-30, Vol. 5 No. 5; 1977-10-29, Vol. 5 No. 17; 1980-10-18, Vol. 8 No. 13; 1982-10-16, Vol. 10 No. 13; 1984-01-14, Vol. 11 No. 25
Gay Light, 1977-07-07
Gay Sunshine, 1974-03-1974-05, No. 21
Gaysweek, 1977-10-10, No. 34
genre, 1995-02, No. 25
Human Rights Campaign Equality, 2015-04-2016-05
mate., 2013-03-2013-05
The New York City News, 1982-03-17, Vol. III No. 18
New York Native, 1983-10-10-1983-10-23, Iss. 74; 1984-03-26-1984-04-08, Iss. 86; 1984-04-23-1984-05-06, Iss. 88; 1984-07-30-1984-08-12, Iss. 95; 1984-11-05-1984-11-18, Iss. 102; 1984-06-17-1984-07-14, Iss. 118-119; 1985-07-29-1985-08-11, Iss. 121; 1985-09-16-1985-09-22, Iss. 126; 1985-10-07-1985-10-20, Iss. 129-130; 1986-02-24, Iss. 149; 1987-01-26, Iss. 197; 1987-03-16, Iss. 204; 1987-05-04, Iss. 211; 1995-06-19, Iss. 635
OUT, 1996-08, No. 35; 1996-10, No. 37; 2011-11, No. 203; 2016-02, No. 251
RFD, 1985-12-1986-02, No. 45